Scenic Hudson Collection: Records Relating to the Storm King Case, 1963-1981
Marist College Archives and Special Collections
- 16. Publicity Materials, 1964-1978; 16; About 3 linear feet Boxes: 157 - 165 Folders: 2068 - 2412
  - Release; 10/25/66 (Folder 2160, Box 157)
  - Release; 10/28/66 (Folder 2161, Box 157)
  - Release: Westport Striped Bass Club; 11/2/66 (Folder 2162, Box 158)
  - Special Bulletin; 11/7/66 (Folder 2163, Box 158)
  - Letter to Charles E. Eble; 11/10/66 (Folder 2164, Box 158)
  - Release - Cornwall Taxpayers Water Protection Ass. 11/10/66 (Folder 2165, Box 158)
  - Release; 11/11/66 (Folder 2166, Box 158)
  - Release; 11/11/66 (Folder 2167, Box 158)
  - Release; 11/14/66 (Folder 2168, Box 158)
  - Release; 11/14/66 (Folder 2169, Box 158)
  - Release; 11/14/66 (Folder 2170, Box 158)
  - Release; 11/28/66 (Folder 2171, Box 158)
  - New Analysis - Air Pollution: Background to Editors; 12/8/66 (Folder 2172, Box 158)
  - Memo re: Con Ed Plan to Relocate Catskill Aqueduct; 12/9/66 (Folder 2173, Box 158)
  - Washington Hearings Report; 12/13/66 (Background to Members) (Folder 2174, Box 158)
  - Memo to Editors; 12/15/66 - Transcript of Part of FPC Hearings on Catskill Aqueduct (Folder 2175, Box 158)
  - Fact Sheet; Dec. 1966 (Folder 2176, Box 158)
  - Carmer Appeal; 12/66 (Folder 2177, Box 158)
  - Release; 1/9/67 (Folder 2178, Box 158)
  - John V. Lindsay Letter (Special Group) 1/9/67 (Folder 2179, Box 158)
  - Release: Georgia Pacific; 1/13/67 (Folder 2180, Box 158)
  - Special Memorandum; 1/31/67 (Folder 2181, Box 158)
  - Release - Air Pollution; 2/11/67 (Folder 2182, Box 158)
  - Memo to S.H. Committee Members; 2/10/67 (Folder 2183, Box 158)
  - Eble Letter: 2/22/67 - Special Group (Folder 2184, Box 158)
  - Release; 2/27/67 (Folder 2185, Box 158)
  - Release; 3/6/67 (Folder 2186, Box 158)
  - Release; 3/8/67 (Folder 2187, Box 158)
  - Statement - Ron Dagon re: Connecticut Fish&Game (Folder 2188, Box 158)
  - Statement to Committee on Fish&Game - Connecticut Bill 4546 3/8/67 (Folder 2189, Box 158)
  - Release; 3/21/67 (Folder 2190, Box 158)
  - Release; 3/28/67 (Folder 2191, Box 158)
  - Release; 4/24/67 (Folder 2192, Box 158)
  - Memo to Editors; 5/17/67 (Folder 2193, Box 158)
  - Background Plea to Members; 5/24/67 (Folder 2194, Box 158)
  - Current Issues in the Storm Over Storm King; May 1967 (Folder 2195, Box 158)
  - Carl Carmer Letter (Special Groups) 6/6/67 (Folder 2196, Box 158)
  - Release - Arras Statement; 6/7/67 (Folder 2197, Box 158)
  - Letter to Editor (re: Sporn Thesis) 6/12/67 (Folder 2198, Box 158)
  - Literature: Striped Bass Protection - H. Philip Arras; 6/13/67 (Folder 2199, Box 158)
  - Release; 6/27/67 (Folder 2200, Box 158)
  - “A Brief Review” June 1967 (Folder 2201, Box 158)
  - Release: 7/7/67 (Folder 2202, Box 158)
  - Notes from Octagon House; 7/11/67 (Folder 2203, Box 158)
  - Releases - re: Partitions; July 17-24, 1968 (Folder 2204, Box 158)
  - Press Release, re: FPC Examiner’s Recommendations 8/6/68; &Releases, re: Storm King - Con Ed (Folder 2205, Box 158)
  - Alert Memo to Editors 8/7/67 (Folder 2206, Box 158)
  - Special Memo to Groups, re: Examiner’s Report; 8/9/68 (Folder 2207, Box 158)
  - Memo to Groups Associated with S.H.; 8/12/68 (Folder 2208, Box 158)
  - Memo to Officers and Committee Members; 8/14/67 (Folder 2209, Box 158)
  - Literature: Point One of Brief - Prepared by Paul, Weiss, Rifkind etc. 8/14/67 (Folder 2210, Box 158)
  - Release&Memo to Editors and Writers; 8/14/67 (Folder 2211, Box 158)
  - Release; 8/17/67 (Folder 2212, Box 158)
  - Memo: Nomination of Robert Boyle - Conservation Communicationist of the Year; 8/22/67 (Folder 2213, Box 158)
  - Memo to Editors: Con Ed Subsidizes Cornwall Support; 8/23/67 (Folder 2214, Box 158)
  - Memo to Editors; 8/30/67 (Folder 2215, Box 158)
  - Memo to Editors: Catskill Aqueduct; 9/1/67 (Folder 2216, Box 158)
  - Release; Sept. 6, 1967 (Folder 2217, Box 158)
  - Memo to Editors: “Patent Trader” The Battle for Storm King; 9/21/67 (Folder 2218, Box 158)
  - Release; Sept. 25, 1967 (Folder 2219, Box 158)
  - SHPC Information Packet; 9/28/67 (Folder 2220, Box 158)
  - To Editors: Gas Turbines; 9/28/67 (Folder 2221, Box 158)
  - Memo to Editors: re Gas Turbine Plants; 10/6/67 (Folder 2222, Box 158)
  - Release Breakneck Ridge; 11/15/67 (Folder 2223, Box 158)
  - Ottinger - Releases; 11/18/67 (Folder 2224, Box 158)
  - Literature: “The Storm King Struggle” 11/18/67 (Folder 2225, Box 158)
  - Remarks of Alexander Aldrich - Boat Trip; 11/18/67 (Folder 2226, Box 158)
  - List of Affiliated Organizations; 11/18/67 (Folder 2227, Box 158)
  - Release: Budget Information; 11/28/67 (Folder 2228, Box 158)
  - General Argument for S.H. 1967 (Folder 2229, Box 158)
  - Release; 1/30/68 (Folder 2230, Box 158)
  - S.H.P.C. Meeting “1968 Committee Needs” 2/20/68 (Folder 2231, Box 158)
  - Literature: Newsletter “This is a Real Progress Report from S.H.” 2/68 (Folder 2232, Box 158)
  - S.H.P.C. - Petitions to FPC; 4/3/68 (Folder 2233, Box 158)
  - To the Editors; 6/26/68 (Folder 2234, Box 158)
  - Release: Rothschild Reception; 6/26/68 (Folder 2235, Box 158)
  - Release (On Expressway) 7/18/68 (Folder 2236, Box 158)
  - Release: Hudson River Fisheries Association; 7/24/68 (Folder 2237, Box 158)
  - FPC Release # 15652 (re: Examiner’s Recommendations) 8/6/68 (Folder 2238, Box 158)
  - Special Memo to Groups Associated with S.H.P.C. in the Storm King Fights (concerns examiner’s recommendation) 8/9/68 (Folder 2239, Box 158)
  - Memo to S.H. Members from Saunders - Concerning FPC Recommendation; 8/12/68 (Folder 2240, Box 158)
  - Memo to Interested Editors (re: Simpson’s Recommendation) 8/14/68 (Folder 2241, Box 158)
  - Pautzke - Udall Package: Sent 9/18/68 to Major Editors, Sports People&Up-River Papers (Approx. 40 Copies) (Folder 2242, Box 158)
  - S.H.P.C. Conservation Organization of the Year - Awarded in Rochester; Release 9/26/68 (Folder 2243, Box 158)
  - Release - Brief; 10/7/68 (Folder 2244, Box 158)
  - Brief on Blackout, Air Pollution&Water to Members; 10/8/68 (Folder 2245, Box 158)
  - Release; 11/22/68 (Folder 2246, Box 158)
  - Release; S.H. Motions 12/20/68 (Folder 2247, Box 158)
  - Special Memo to Conservation Leaders; 1/9/69 (Folder 2248, Box 159)
  - Release re: Readers Digest Article; 1/23/69 (Folder 2249, Box 159)
  - S.H. Publicity Releases; 2/14/69 (Folder 2250, Box 159)
  - Release: Wildlife Conservation Award; 2/17/69 (Folder 2251, Box 159)
  - Release: Wildlife Conservation Award (L.I.) 2/17/69 (Folder 2252, Box 159)
  - Memo to Editors re: Conservation Award 1968; 2/27/69 (Folder 2253, Box 159)
  - Water Resources Statement; March 14, 1969 (Folder 2254, Box 159)
  - Release - re: Palisades Interstate Park; 3/18/69 (Folder 2255, Box 159)
  - WOR Radio - RV on the McCanns; 4/24/69 (Folder 2256, Box 159)
  - Status Report - Quarterly Background to Members; June 1969 (Folder 2257, Box 159)
  - Radio&TV Reports - Vandivert and Boyle on NBC; 6/4/69 (Folder 2258, Box 159)
  - Letter to Luce; 7/31/69 (Folder 2259, Box 159)
  - Release; 8/8/69 (Folder 2260, Box 159)
  - Conservation Meeting; 8/14/69 (Folder 2261, Box 159)
  - Memo to Editors - Events Con Ed Ignored (Quotes) 8/19/69 (Folder 2262, Box 159)
  - Sloop Release; 8/26/69 (Folder 2263, Box 159)
  - Sloop Follow-up Release; 8/29/69 (Folder 2264, Box 159)
  - Legal Meeting; 9/18/69 (Folder 2265, Box 159)
  - Utilities&The Hudson River (Conservation Council Meeting; 9/27/69 (Folder 2266, Box 159)
  - Release “Thermal Pollution” Lake Placid; 9/27/69 (Folder 2267, Box 159)
  - Special Memo to Conservationists, 10/9/69 (Folder 2268, Box 159)
  - Statement - NYS Legislative Committee on Environmental Management; 10/23/69 (Folder 2269, Box 159)
  - Release - Fish Study; 10/27/69 (Folder 2270, Box 159)
  - HRFA Release; 11/15/69 (Folder 2271, Box 159)
  - Protection of Registered Historic Site; 11/1969 (Folder 2272, Box 159)
  - Public Service Commission - Memo to S.H. Members; 12/5/69 (Folder 2273, Box 159)
  - Glenn Harris at S.P.H.C. 12/9/69 (Folder 2274, Box 159)
  - Statement - Rod Vandivert, New Paltz, re: H.R. Fish Study; 12/11/69 (Folder 2275, Box 159)
  - Alternatives; 12/17/69 (Folder 2276, Box 159)
  - Package; 12/69 (Folder 2277, Box 159)
  - Importance of Storm King Case; 12/69 (Folder 2278, Box 159)
  - Background with NY Magazine Article; 1969 (Folder 2279, Box 159)
  - Saunders Letter; 12/69 (Folder 2280, Box 159)
  - Blaming Conservationists Campaign; 1969 (Folder 2281, Box 159)
  - American Heritage Release; 1/12/70 (Folder 2282, Box 159)
  - Forecast; 1/21/70 (Folder 2283, Box 159)
  - Hudson River Association Release; 1/28/70 (Folder 2284, Box 159)
  - Fortune Magazine on Environment; 1/30/70 (Folder 2285, Box 159)
  - Water Quality (Magazine - Environmental Science& Technology) (Pollution) Jan. 1970 (Folder 2286, Box 159)
  - Fish Kill Indian Point Release of S.H. 2/3/70 (Folder 2287, Box 159)
  - Kilborne Letter re: Fish; 2/6/70 (Folder 2288, Box 159)
  - Release re: Yonkers (Church Groups) re: Charles Luce 3/17/70 (Folder 2289, Box 159)
  - HRFA - Mailing to Members; March 1970 (Folder 2290, Box 159)
  - Importance of Storm King Case; March 1970 (Folder 2291, Box 159)
  - Release re: Earth Day; 4/22/70 (Folder 2292, Box 159)
  - NYC Release re: Oral Arguments; 5/7/70 (Folder 2293, Box 159)
  - Harvard Black Rock Forest - Important Points; 5/19/70 (Folder 2294, Box 159)
  - Release re: Summer Crisis; 7/24/70 (Folder 2295, Box 159)
  - Gas Turbine Background Sheet; July 1970 (Folder 2296, Box 159)
  - Memo to Editors; 9/17/70 (Folder 2297, Box 159)
  - Release re: Applications for Rehearing; 9/17/70 (Folder 2298, Box 159)
  - Vandivert Statement - NYS Conservation Convention; 9/26/70 (Folder 2299, Box 159)
  - Memo to Editors re: NYC; 10/3/70 (Folder 2300, Box 159)
  - HRFA Release re: Fish Studies; 11/19/70 (Folder 2301, Box 159)
  - U.S. Court of Appeals Release; 12/10/70 (Folder 2302, Box 159)
  - Saunders; 12/18/70 (Folder 2303, Box 159)
  - Editorial (S.H.) NBC TV, Reply; 2/8/71 (Folder 2304, Box 159)
  - Special Memo to Scenic Hudson Officers and Contributors; 3/1/71 (Folder 2305, Box 159)
  - Jet Turbine (Reprints) 1971 (Folder 2306, Box 159)
  - American Youth Hostels Release; 3/16/70 (Folder 2307, Box 159)
  - Alternatives - Gas Turbines; March 1971 (Folder 2308, Box 159)
  - Memo to Editors re: Filing of Con Ed Brief; 4/9/71 (Folder 2309, Box 159)
  - Memo to Board re: Pumped Storage and Gas Turbines; 4/27/71 (Folder 2310, Box 159)
  - Editors Concerned with NYC Power Situation; 4/20/71 (Folder 2311, Box 159)
  - Background - Gas Turbines; May 1971 (Folder 2312, Box 159)
  - Playboy; May 1971 (Folder 2313, Box 159)
  - Background Members: Diamond Decision; 8/71 (Folder 2314, Box 159)
  - Memo (Selvage, Lee&Howard) 9/17/71 (Folder 2315, Box 159)
  - Background to Conservation Leaders: Court of Appeals; Oct. 1971 (Folder 2316, Box 159)
  - Rehearing: Court of Appeals; 11/5/71 (Folder 2317, Box 159)
  - Re: Aqueduct; 11/12/71 (Folder 2318, Box 159)
  - Re: En Banc Decision; 12/2/71 (Folder 2319, Box 159)
  - NYS Supreme Court filing re: Water Quality; 12/15/71 (Folder 2320, Box 159)
  - Re: Con Ed’s 20Year Plan; 2/1/72 (Folder 2321, Box 160)
  - Release re: State Court Action; 2/11/72 (Folder 2322, Box 160)
  - Release re: Editorial&Fact Sheet on Position; 8/22/72 (Folder 2323, Box 160)
  - S.H. Letter to Con Ed re: Future Plans of H.R. 11/17/72 (Folder 2324, Box 160)
  - DEC Speak Out: Saunders and RV; 1972 (Folder 2325, Box 160)
  - Hudson River Day Liner Promotion; 1972 (Folder 2326, Box 160)
  - Releases; 1972 (Folder 2327, Box 160)
  - Legal Hurdles; July 5, 1973 (Folder 2328, Box 160)
  - Con Ed Arrogant, Premature; 7/25/73 (Folder 2329, Box 160)
  - Answer to Con Ed Ad - Press - 7/31/73 (Folder 2330, Box 160)
  - Saunders Letter to Cornwall Local - Legal Steps; 6/28/73 (Folder 2331, Box 160)
  - Sen. Abe Ribicoff - Speech; Sunday Dec. 7, 1973 (Folder 2332, Box 160)
  - Why Con Ed Can’t; 8/17/73 (Folder 2333, Box 160)
  - Equal Time to Con Ed Ad; 8/29/73 (Folder 2334, Box 160)
  - Con Ed Transmission Failures Letter; 9/13/73 (Folder 2335, Box 160)
  - Post Aqueduct 10/11/73 (Folder 2336, Box 160)
  - Saunders Op Ed Letter; 10/15/73 (Folder 2337, Box 160)
  - Corps of Engineers; 11/1/73 (Folder 2338, Box 160)
  - AEC Report 12/8/73 (Folder 2339, Box 160)
  - AEC Report 12/10/73 (Folder 2340, Box 160)
  - U.S. District Courts - Corps Permits; 12/28/73 (Folder 2341, Box 160)
  - L.I. Woman named Pres. of S.H. Group; 1973 (Folder 2342, Box 160)
  - Washington D.C. 1/29/74 (Folder 2343, Box 160)
  - Washington D.C. Briefing; 1/30/74 (Folder 2344, Box 160)
  - Ted Kennedy FPC Request; 2/4/74 (Folder 2345, Box 160)
  - Congressman Koch Letter to the FPC; 2/4/74 (Folder 2346, Box 160)
  - Congressional Hearing set on Storm King Project; 2/11/74 (Folder 2347, Box 160)
  - 12 Congressmen urge FPC to Reopen Hearing on Storm King Plant; 2/15/74 (Folder 2348, Box 160)
  - Pre-Subcommittee; 2/18/74 (Folder 2349, Box 160)
  - Sen. Kennedy renews Appeal for new FPC Storm King Hearings; 2/20/74 (Folder 2350, Box 160)
  - Letter- SHPC to Newspapers; 3/8/74 (Folder 2351, Box 160)
  - Storm King/PSC Hearings; 3/18/74 (Folder 2352, Box 160)
  - Con Edison Mock Ground-Breaking is Termed Insult to Public; 4/10/74 (Folder 2353, Box 160)
  - Press Releases from Scenic Hudson; 4/25/74 (Folder 2354, Box 160)
  - Scenic Hudson Press Release: New FPC Hearing Ordered on Storm King; 5/9/74 (Folder 2355, Box 160)
  - FPC Petitioned to Stay Storm King Construction; 5/10/74 (Folder 2356, Box 160)
  - EPA Recommends Halt in Work on Storm King Plant; 5/14/74 (Folder 2357, Box 160)
  - Storm King Plant Raises Opposition from 31 States, D.C., 6/3/74 (Folder 2358, Box 160)
  - Statement by A.K. Butzel; 12/74 (Folder 2359, Box 160)
  - Storm King FPC Hearing Press Conference; 12/74 (Folder 2360, Box 160)
  - Commissioner Biganne Attacks Storm King: Rod Vandivert; 12/5/74 (Folder 2361, Box 160)
  - Requests for Speakers; 1974 (Folder 2362, Box 160)
  - Environmental Groups Petition FPC to Revoke Con Ed’s Storm King License; 1/6/75 (Folder 2363, Box 160)
  - Interior Department Moves to Reopen License Hearings on Storm King; 1/30/75 (Folder 2364, Box 160)
  - Rod Vandivert Elected to SHPC Board; 11/75 (Folder 2365, Box 160)
  - (Vandivert) PSB Statement: PCB Crisis; 12/12/75 (Folder 2366, Box 160)
  - SHPC Calls for Complete Program of PCB Disposal; 1/76 (Folder 2367, Box 160)
  - Dyson Misses Issue; 3/3/76 (Folder 2368, Box 160)
  - SH Attacks Con Ed’s Storm King Study; 3/8/76 (Folder 2369, Box 160)
  - Brochure: A Friend of the River; 5/20/76 (Folder 2370, Box 160)
  - Idaho’s Teton River Dam&One Proposed on Hudson by Con Ed; 6/8/76 (Folder 2371, Box 160)
  - Release; 1978 (Folder 2372, Box 160)
  - Literature: “As One who is Directly Involved in Camping…” Undated (Folder 2373, Box 160)
  - Fact Sheet (Sierra Club) (Folder 2374, Box 160)
  - “Danger Con Ed at Storm King” sheet (Folder 2375, Box 160)
  - Resolutions re: Advisory Council (Folder 2376, Box 160)
  - Re: Release of Publicity Costs, Con Ed and Scenic Hudson (Folder 2377, Box 160)
  - Statement by Rod Vandivert to Commission, n.d. (Folder 2378, Box 160)
  - Publicity; 1964-Misc. (Folder 2379, Box 160)
  - Publicity Campaign; 1964 (Folder 2380, Box 160)
  - Publicity Material; 1965 Miscellaneous (Folder 2381, Box 161)
  - R.V. Statements and Articles, SHPC; 1965 (Folder 2382, Box 161)
  - Publicity Material; 1966 Miscellaneous (Folder 2383, Box 161)
  - Publicity Material; 1967 Miscellaneous (Folder 2384, Box 161)
  - Publicity Material; 1968 Miscellaneous (Folder 2385, Box 161)
  - Publicity Material; 1969 Miscellaneous (Folder 2386, Box 161)
  - Publicity Material; 1970-72 Miscellaneous (Folder 2387, Box 161)
  - Publicity Material; Undated Miscellaneous (Folder 2388, Box 161)
  - Publicity Material; Undated Miscellaneous (Folder 2389, Box 161)
  - Ads for Scenic Hudson (Drafts) (Folder 2390, Box 162)
  - Brochures (Folder 2391, Box 162)
  - Bulletins (Folder 2392, Box 162)
  - John Zeigler Inc. Advertising Agency (Folder 2393, Box 162)
  - Memoranda; 1964-68 (Folder 2394, Box 162)
  - Memoranda; 1969-72 (Folder 2395, Box 162)
  - New England’s First Extra High Voltage Line: Press Kit (Folder 2396, Box 162)
  - Reprints of News Articles (Folder 2397, Box 162)
  - Scenic Hudson Information Kit (Folder 2398, Box 162)
  - Scenic Hudson Press Kit (Folder 2399, Box 162)
  - Scenic Hudson Information Kit; 1966-67 (Folder 2400, Box 163)
  - Scenic Hudson: Publicity Kit (Folder 2401, Box 163)
  - Hudson River&Its Painters (Folder 2402, Box 163)
  - Scenic Hudson Preservation Conference (Deserves Your Support) (Folder 2403, Box 163)
  - Storm Over Storm King Mountain (Folder 2404, Box 163)
  - Testimony - Joint Legislative Committee on Natural Resources - Hearings at Bear Mountain Inn; Nov. 19&20, 1964 (Folder 2405, Box 163)
  - 1964 Hudson Valley Project Releases (Folder 2406, Box 163)
  - Releases; 1964-65 (Folder 2407, Box 163)
  - SHPC Releases; 1964-66 (Folder 2408, Box 164)
  - Mailings; 1965-66 (Folder 2409, Box 164)
  - Releases; 1968 (Folder 2410, Box 164)
  - SHPC: Con Ed Confrontation re: Heat Waves; Summer 1969 (Folder 2411, Box 165)
  - SHPC: Newspaper Correspondence, Political Correspondence; 1969-1970 (Folder 2412, Box 165)
- 17. Clippings, 17; About 7 linear feet Boxes: 167 - 183 > Folders: 2418 - 2606
  Jan. 1965 Lou Frankel - Clippings Through Jan. 1965
  - Clippings; 11/30/61, 8/26/61, 10/7/63 (Folder 2418, Box 167)
  - Jan. 30 - Feb. 2, 1964 (Folder 2419, Box 167)
  - July 30 - Aug. 5, 1964 (Folder 2420, Box 167)
  - Aug. 6 - Aug. 13, 1964 (Folder 2421, Box 167)
  - Aug. 14 - Aug. 21, 1964 (Folder 2422, Box 167)
  - Aug. 22 - Aug. 29, 1964 (Folder 2423, Box 167)
  - Aug. 30 - Sept. 5, 1964 (Folder 2424, Box 167)
  - Sept. 6 - Sept. 13, 1964 (Folder 2425, Box 167)
  - Sept. 14 - Sept. 21, 1964 (Folder 2426, Box 167)
  - Sept. 22 - Sept. 29, 2964 (Folder 2427, Box 167)
  - Sept. 30 - Oct. 7, 1964 (Folder 2428, Box 167)
  - Oct. 8 - Oct. 15, 1964 (Folder 2429, Box 167)
  - Oct. 16 - Oct. 23, 1964 (Folder 2430, Box 167)
  - Oct. 24 - Oct. 31, 1964 (Folder 2431, Box 167)
  - Nov. 1 - Nov. 8, 1964 (Folder 2432, Box 167)
  - Nov. 9 - Nov. 16, 1964 (Folder 2433, Box 167)
  - Nov. 17 - Nov. 24, 1964 (Folder 2434, Box 167)
  - Nov. 25 - Dec. 2, 1964 (Folder 2435, Box 167)
  - Dec. 3 - Dec. 10, 1964 (Folder 2436, Box 167)
  - Dec. 11 - Dec. 18, 1964 (Folder 2437, Box 167)
  - Dec. 19 - Dec. 26, 1964 (Folder 2438, Box 167)
  - Dec. 27 - Jan. 3, 1965 (Folder 2439, Box 167)
  - Jan. 4 - Jan. 11, 1965 (Folder 2440, Box 167)
  - Jan. 12 - Jan. 19, 1965 (Folder 2441, Box 167)
  - Jan. 20 - Jan. 27, 1965 (Folder 2442, Box 167)
  - Jan. 28 - Feb 4, 1965 (Folder 2443, Box 167)
  - Feb. 5 - Feb. 12, 1965 (Folder 2444, Box 167)
  - Clippings; Dec. 18, 1964 - Jan. 7, 1965 (Folder 2445, Box 168)
  - Jan. 8 - Jan. 15, 1965 (Folder 2446, Box 168)
  - Jan. 16 - Jan. 23, 1965 (Folder 2447, Box 168)
  - Jan. 24 - Jan. 31, 1965 (Folder 2448, Box 168)
  - Feb. 1 - Feb. 8, 1965 (Folder 2449, Box 168)
  - Feb. 9 - Feb 16, 1965 (Folder 2450, Box 168)
  - Feb 17 - Feb. 24, 1965 (Folder 2451, Box 168)
  - Feb. 1 - Feb. 7, 1965 (Folder 2452, Box 169)
  - Feb. 8 - Feb. 15, 1965 (Folder 2453, Box 169)
  - Feb. 16 - Feb. 23, 1965 (Folder 2454, Box 169)
  - Feb. 24 - March 3, 1965 (Folder 2455, Box 169)
  - March 4 - March 11, 1965 (Folder 2456, Box 169)
  - March 12 - March 19, 1965 (Folder 2457, Box 169)
  - March 20 - March 27, 1965 (Folder 2458, Box 169)
  - March 30 - April 6, 1965 (Folder 2459, Box 169)
  - April 7 - April 14, 1965 (Folder 2460, Box 169)
  - April 15 - April 22, 1965 (Folder 2461, Box 169)
  - April 23 - April 30, 1965 (Folder 2462, Box 169)
  - Scenic Hudson Clippings: Lou Frankel; May 1965 (Folder 2463, Box 170)
  - Blackout; Nov. 9, 1965 (Folder 2464, Box 170)
  - Blackout; Nov. 9, 1965 (Folder 2465, Box 170)
  - Clippings; May 1965 (Folder 2466, Box 170)
  - Clips - 1965 (Folder 2467, Box 170)
  - Clippings; 1965 (Folder 2468, Box 171)
  - FPC Hearing Clippings; 1966 (Folder 2469, Box 171)
  - FPC Hearing Clippings; 1966 (Folder 2470, Box 171)
  - FPC Hearing Clippings; 1966 (Folder 2471, Box 171)
  - Clippings; 1966 (Folder 2472, Box 171)
  - Clippings; 1966 (Folder 2473, Box 171)
  - Clippings; 1966 (Folder 2474, Box 172)
  - Clippings; 1966 (Folder 2475, Box 172)
  - Clippings; 1967 (Folder 2476, Box 172)
  - Clippings; 1967 (Folder 2477, Box 172)
  - Clippings; 1967 (Folder 2478, Box 172)
  - FPC - Hearings Clippings; Jan. - June 1967 (Folder 2479, Box 173)
  - FPC Hearings; 1967 (Folder 2480, Box 173)
  - FPC Hearings; 1967 (Folder 2481, Box 173)
  - FPC Hearings; 1967 (Folder 2482, Box 173)
  - FPC Hearings; 1967 (Folder 2483, Box 173)
  - FPC Hearings; 1967 (Folder 2484, Box 173)
  - FPC Clippings; 1968 (Folder 2485, Box 174)
  - Editorials&Letters to the Editor for Scenic Hudson; 1968-70 (Folder 2486, Box 174)
  - Clippings - Other than New York City; Sept. 1968 - July 24, 1970 (Folder 2487, Box 174)
  - Clippings - Other than New York City; Sept. 1968 - July 24, 1970 (Folder 2488, Box 174)
  - Clippings - Other than New York City; Sept. 1968 - July 24, 1970 (Folder 2489, Box 174)
  - Clippings - New York City Papers; Oct. 17, 1968 - July 30, 1970 (Folder 2490, Box 174)
  - Clippings; 1969 (Folder 2491, Box 175)
  - Clippings; Con Edison; Aug. 26, 1968 - Sept. 8, 1969 (Folder 2492, Box 175)
  - Clippings; Con Edison; Aug. 26, 1968 - Sept. 8, 1969 (Folder 2493, Box 175)
  - Clippings; Con Edison; Aug. 26, 1968 - Sept. 8, 1969 (Folder 2494, Box 175)
  - Clippings; 1970 (Folder 2495, Box 175)
  - Con Ed Clips; Sept. 1969 - Aug. 31, 1970 (Folder 2496, Box 176)
  - Con Ed Clips; Sept. 1969 - Aug. 31, 1970 (Folder 2497, Box 176)
  - Con Ed Clips; Sept. 1969 - Aug. 31, 1970 (Folder 2498, Box 176)
  - Con Ed Clips; Sept. 1969 - Aug. 31, 1970 (Folder 2499, Box 176)
  - Con Ed Clips; Sept. 1, 1970 - Dec. 31, 1970 (Folder 2500, Box 176)
  - Clippings; 1971 (Folder 2501, Box 177)
  - Clippings; 1971 (Folder 2502, Box 177)
  - Clippings - Brownouts; 1971 (Folder 2503, Box 177)
  - Scenic Hudson Clips; 1971 (Folder 2504, Box 177)
  - Con Ed Clips; 1971 (Folder 2505, Box 177)
  - Editorials&Letters to Editors; 1971 (Folder 2506, Box 177)
  - Con Ed, 1972 (does not include Storm King or Power Crisis) (Folder 2507, Box 178)
  - Power Crisis, 1972 (Folder 2508, Box 178)
  - Clippings, 1972 (Folder 2509, Box 178)
  - Clippings, 1972 (Folder 2510, Box 178)
  - Clippings, 1972 (Folder 2511, Box 178)
  - August 30, 1970 (Folder 2512, Box 179)
  - January 11 - Jan. 18, 1973 (Folder 2513, Box 179)
  - Feb. 4 - Feb. 11, 1973 (Folder 2514, Box 179)
  - Feb. 12 - Feb. 19, 1973 (Folder 2515, Box 179)
  - Feb. 28 - March 6, 1973 (Folder 2516, Box 179)
  - March 7 - March 14, 1973 (Folder 2517, Box 179)
  - March 15 - March 22, 1973 (Folder 2518, Box 179)
  - March 23 - March 30, 1973 (Folder 2519, Box 179)
  - March 31 - April 6, 1973 (Folder 2520, Box 179)
  - April 7 - 14, 1973 (Folder 2521, Box 179)
  - April 15 - April 22, 1973 (Folder 2522, Box 179)
  - April 23 - April 30, 1973 (Folder 2523, Box 179)
  - April 31 - May 6, 1973 (Folder 2524, Box 179)
  - May 7 - May 15, 1973 (Folder 2525, Box 179)
  - May 16 - May 23, 1973 (Folder 2526, Box 179)
  - May 24 - May 31, 1973 (Folder 2527, Box 179)
  - June 1 - June 8, 1973 (Folder 2528, Box 179)
  - June 9 - June 16, 1973 (Folder 2529, Box 179)
  - June 17 - June 24, 1973 (Folder 2530, Box 179)
  - June 25 - July 1, 1973 (Folder 2531, Box 179)
  - July 2 - July 9, 1973 (Folder 2532, Box 179)
  - July 10 - July 17, 1973 (Folder 2533, Box 179)
  - July 18 - July 25, 1973 (Folder 2534, Box 179)
  - July 26 - August 2, 1973 (Folder 2535, Box 179)
  - Aug. 3 - Aug. 10, 1973 (Folder 2536, Box 179)
  - Aug. 11 - Aug. 18, 1973 (Folder 2537, Box 179)
  - Aug. 19 - Aug. 26, 1973 (Folder 2538, Box 179)